Robert Ferrer

I'm Brazilian, have always worked with customer service, with over 20 years of experience. I am an observer, analyst and have an entrepreneurial vision, I have the ability to work as a team, as a collaborator I always try to be active in projects to achieve the desired success, seeking to leverage merchandising, up selling and customer service.

Experience

2013-08- Business and Services Manager

2022-04 Santander Bank, Jaú, SP Brazil

Customer service, opening accounts, sale of financial services, insurance, telephone and visits, perform the cashier function.

₂₀₀₃₋₁₀₋ Salesman

2011-09 Magazine Luiza, Jaú, SP Brazil

Worked 5 years as a salesperson in all sectors and position the cashier for 3 years.

Functions and sectors worked were cashier, treasury assistant, furniture, appliances, toys, technology and cell phones

Education

2021-07- Systems Developer

2022-12 ETEC - Etec Joaquim Ferreira do Amaral

2014-06- MBA in Administration and Finance

2015-12 UNINTER International University Center

2013-02- **Specialization** in Production Engineering

2014-06 UNINTER International University Center

2007-02- **Bachelor** Business Administration

2010-12 Integrated Colleges of Jaú

Certification and Licenses

2021-05- Verified International Academic Qualifications

Not expire WES Word Education Services

2019-02- Elderly Caregiver

Not expire UNIMED National Confederation of Medical Cooperatives

₂₀₁₄₋₀₁₋ CPA-10

2023-12 ANBIMA Brazilian Association of Financial and Capital Markets

Volunteer work

2015-10- Volunteer - Community Alliance of Mercy

2018-12 October 2015 - December 2018

We collect food and distribute it to homeless people once a week

Personal info

Number Phone and Skype +55 14 99860-8309

E-mail:

ferrerrobert@outlook.com

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/robertferrer7/

GitHub

https://github.com/RobertFe rrer7

Nationality

Brazilian

Skills

Administration
Sales Management
Customer Service
Interpersonal Communication
Cash handling & POS
Time Management
Finances

Hobby

Writer, I am the author of the book:
"Do not be bad".

Martial arts